mycarforum.com 2015-04-09

# MCF Terms Of Service - Official Announcements - MyCarForum.com

**Disclaimer**

You agree not to use this forum to post any material that is vulgar, defamatory, inaccurate, harassing, hateful, threatening, invasive of the privacy of others, sexually explicit, or illegal. You also agree that you will not post any copyrighted material that is not owned by you or MyCarForum. 

You remain solely responsible for the content of your messages, and you agree to indemnify and hold harmless this forum and their agents with respect to any claim based upon any post you may submit. MyCarForum reserves the right to reveal any information we have about you in the event of a complaint or legal action arising from any message that you may post.

MyCarForum takes absolutely no responsibility for the way you use the information provided on this forum. These links for files and anything else on this forum are here for private purposes only and should not be viewed whatsoever!

Any posts in the MyCarForum forum are posted by individuals acting in their own right and do not necessarily reflect the views of MyCarForum.

 **Privacy Policy**

MyCarForum takes your privacy seriously. We has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for MyCarForum.

 **Types of Information We Collect**

Generally, you are free to browse the MyCarForum site without submitting any personal information. We do not collect any of your personal information (such as a name, address or email address) when you visit the MyCarForum, unless you register or have registered to use our forum, or otherwise agree to submit to us such information.

 **Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site.

 **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

MyCarForum will not sell, license or disclose your personal information to any third party for commercial reasons without your consent. MyCarForum will at our discretion reveal personal information when it deem necessary.

 **Password Encryption**

Please note that registration in our forum require that you specify a password for your use. This password is then encrypted by our forums automatically, which means that the staff of MyCarForum does not have access or knowledge of what your exact password is. This gives you ample security in case you are using the same password repeatedly in other sites (which is discouraged).

 **What are Cookies? Why do we use them?**

MyCarForum uses browser cookies to facilitate your experience with our services and site features. These cookies are small sections of code that our server sends to your browser which it can then store on your hard drive.

If you choose to accept these cookies, they enable us to recognize that your browser has previously visited and used our site and its services and, based on your browser's previous visits, assist us with tailoring the information, content and technical support you will receive.

An example of the customization allowed by the use of such cookies is to retain your username and password as part of the MyCarForum forums on our site so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit.

These cookies do not collect, store or maintain your private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit the MyCarForum, and you can choose to refuse our cookie, delete our cookie from your hard drive.

Third party vendor, such as Google, uses cookies to serve ads on MyCarForum. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to MyCarForum and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "External link").

 **Registration Forms**

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, etc).

 **External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. MyCarForum is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Public Forums**

This site makes message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

 **Postings on Message Boards**

It is important for you to remain aware that when you provide personal information (e.g., name, address, phone number) in a posting on any message board, that information is available to any other person or user having access and use of that message board, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you.

 **Your Consent to this Policy**

By using our Site, you agree to this Policy. This document supersedes any prior communication on this topic and reflects the entire and exclusive Privacy Policy for this Site. We may change our Policy by posting a new version of it on our Site at any time.

 **Legal Stuff**

We are posting this Policy to be a good web citizen. This site operates in good faith, but on an AS-IS, AS-AVAILABLE BASIS. Any warranties of accuracy, quality, title, fitness or merchantibility are disclaimed. We are not liable for direct, indirect, incidental or consequential damages. We are not liable for events beyond our direct control.

 **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can reach us at [support@mycarforum.com](mailto:support@mycarforum.com "External link") .

 **Right to Change Policy**

As MyCarForum is constantly innovating and enhancing the type of services it provides to its users, this Privacy Statement will also continue to change to match the services and features we make available. As such, we reserve the right to change this statement to match the services we provide.
